<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE ichicsr>
<ichicsr lang="en">
<ichicsrmessageheader>
<messagetype>ichicsr</messagetype>
<messageformatversion>2.1</messageformatversion>
<messageformatrelease>1.0</messageformatrelease>
<messagenumb>a6c9db72-9fff-11ee-8305-28dfeb6bed73-BIO</messagenumb>
<messagesenderidentifier>simplesafety</messagesenderidentifier>
<messagereceiveridentifier>ss</messagereceiveridentifier>
<messagedateformat>204</messagedateformat>

</ichicsrmessageheader>
<safetyreport>




<transmissiondateformat>102</transmissiondateformat>

<reporttype>1</reporttype>
<serious>0</serious>






<receivedateformat>102</receivedateformat>
<receivedate>20230403</receivedate>
<receiptdateformat>102</receiptdateformat>
<receiptdate>20230403</receiptdate>

<companynumb>simplesafety_ss_2217007394</companynumb>



<sender>

<senderorganization>simplesafety</senderorganization>
</sender>
<receiver>

<receiverorganization>ss</receiverorganization>
</receiver>
<patient>
<patientinitial>unknown</patientinitial>
















<patientmedicalhistorytext>UNK.</patientmedicalhistorytext>

<reaction>
<primarysourcereaction>Patient feels weak while walking </primarysourcereaction>





<reactionstartdateformat>102</reactionstartdateformat>

<reactionenddateformat>102</reactionenddateformat>





<reactionoutcome>3</reactionoutcome>
</reaction><reaction>
<primarysourcereaction>Patient uses bathroom for urination frequently for every 20 minutes.</primarysourcereaction>





<reactionstartdateformat>102</reactionstartdateformat>

<reactionenddateformat>102</reactionenddateformat>





<reactionoutcome>3</reactionoutcome>
</reaction><drug>
<drugcharacterization>1</drugcharacterization>
<medicinalproduct>unknown</medicinalproduct>




<drugauthorizationholder>NA</drugauthorizationholder>












<drugstartdateformat>102</drugstartdateformat>

<drugenddateformat>102</drugenddateformat>






<activesubstance>
<activesubstancename>unknown</activesubstancename>
</activesubstance>
</drug><drug>
<drugcharacterization>2</drugcharacterization>
<medicinalproduct>UNK</medicinalproduct>




<drugauthorizationholder>NA</drugauthorizationholder>







<drugdosagetext>UNK .D .</drugdosagetext>




<drugstartdateformat>102</drugstartdateformat>

<drugenddateformat>102</drugenddateformat>






<activesubstance>
<activesubstancename>UNK</activesubstancename>
</activesubstance>
</drug><summary>
<narrativeincludeclinical>
DESRCRIPTION OF THE ADVERSE EVENT:
Initial report date: 03-APR-2023 Information received from male patient, who was using Gabapentin 300 mg capsules manufactured by Invagen. Height, weight and ethnicity of the patient was unknown. He was unable to provide NDC, and lot number, however provided the imprints as IG 322 300 mg yellow capsule, expiry date 19-MAR-2024. Medical history and concurrent conditions and concomitant medications were unknown. The patient commenced Gabapentin 300 mg capsules with unknown batch number, expiry date 19-MAR-2024, from unknown date. Dose, frequency, route of administration and indication was unknown. Patient informed that he feels weak while walking and also uses bathroom for urination frequently for every 20 minutes. Information regarding treatment, lab tests were unknown. Action taken with the suspect product was ongoing. Outcome of the events was ongoing. He provided consent to call back. Before collecting or proving any information, call got disconnected abruptly.  Manufacturer Invagen Sub Classification Resolutions Resolution Resolution Type AE Documented Transfer Documents No documents have been attached to this case Owner MARY QStatus Completed Completed On 04/Apr/2023 7:23 AM **Note: All Long Dates are in LOCAL Time Zone.
DATE SALES REPRESENTATIVE INFORMED:
3. SUSPECT PRODUCT INFORMATION : A. INDICATION: UNK B. PRODUCT START DATE: UNK  C. PRODUCT STOP DATE: Ongoing. 4. DEATH INFORMATION A. DATE OF DEATH (If died): NA B. AUTOPSY (YES/NO/UNKNOWN): NA C. DATE OF AUTOPSY: NA 5. SERIOUSNESS CRITERIA (DEATH/LIFE-THREATENING/NEW OR PROLONGED HOSPITALIZATION/DISABILITY/CONGENITAL ANOMALY/IME): NA. 6. EVENT INFORMATION: A. EVENT TERM: 1. Patient feels weak while walking 2. Patient uses bathroom for urination frequently for every 20 minutes. B. START DATE OF EVENT: 1. UNK 2. UNK C. STOP DATE OF EVENT: 1. Ongoing 2. Ongoing D. OUTCOME (NOT RECOVERED/UNKNOWN/RECOVERING/RECOVERED): 1. NOT RECOVERED 2. NOT RECOVERED E. DE-CHALLENGE (POSITIVE/NEGATIVE/UNKNOWN/NOT APPLICABLE): NOT APPLICABLE F. RE-CHALLENGE (POSITIVE/NEGATIVE/UNKNOWN/NOT APPLICABLE): NOT APPLICABLE 7. PAST MEDICAL HISTORY: UNK. 8. ALLERGIES: UNK. 9. CONCOMITANT MEDICATIONS: UNK A. CONCOMITANT NAME: UNK B. CONCOMITANT INDICATION: UNK C. CONCOMITANT DOSE/FREQUENCY: UNK .D . CONCOMITANT START DATE: UNK E. CONCOMITANT STOP DATE: UNK 10. PREGNANCY INFORMATION (YES or NO): NA IF YES A. GESTATION PERIOD: NA B. PREGNANCY OUTCOME: NA C. LAST MENSTRUAL PERIOD DATE: NA D. EXPECTED DATE OF DELIVERY: NA E. NUMBER OF CHILDREN (PRIOR TO PREGNANCY): NA Qinecsa Case: CIPAE23-0234 Page 4 of 5 Run on Wednesday, May 24, 2023 08:50 AM 11. DESRCRIPTION OF THE ADVERSE EVENT: Initial report date: 03-APR-2023 Information received from male patient, who was using Gabapentin 300 mg capsules manufactured by Invagen. Height, weight and ethnicity of the patient was unknown. He was unable to provide NDC, and lot number, however provided the imprints as IG 322 300 mg yellow capsule, expiry date 19-MAR-2024. Medical history and concurrent conditions and concomitant medications were unknown. The patient commenced Gabapentin 300 mg capsules with unknown batch number, expiry date 19-MAR-2024, from unknown date. Dose, frequency, route of administration and indication was unknown. Patient informed that he feels weak while walking and also uses bathroom for urination frequently for every 20 minutes. Information regarding treatment, lab tests were unknown. Action taken with the suspect product was ongoing. Outcome of the events was ongoing. He provided consent to call back. Before collecting or proving any information, call got disconnected abruptly. Qinecsa Case: CIPAE23-0234 Page 5 of 5 Run on Wednesday, May 24, 2023 08:50 AM Manufacturer Invagen Sub Classification Resolutions Resolution Resolution Type AE Documented Transfer Documents No documents have been attached to this case Owner MARY QStatus Completed Completed On 04/Apr/2023 7:23 AM **Note: All Long Dates are in LOCAL Time Zone.</narrativeincludeclinical>
</summary></patient></safetyreport>
</ichicsr>